Summertime. Perfect time to get to know my mans.
I gotta find a cute little festival to take them to.
What about that fireworks show nearby?
Eh, I'd like to go, but that show's always super crowded.
Plus, there's a little local festival right here that day.
We talking full yukata?
OMG, tiny in a yukata!
I'm gonna die of thirst in front of everybody!
I meet you, you gots to figure out you're fit.
I got the man to ask out first!
Don't you gots finals to study for?
I want to send you a heart.
Sine, cosine, tangent.
The heart is wide open.
The wind is running.
I remember it.
Flaring.
The wind is running.
I mean, you don't want to know maybe.
I wanted to cook for the feel- Wiring.
The wind is running.
What you競技 and me to win.
Like that, you listen to me humane.
ところでer up here.
So go ahead and leave yourself
Your mind my body
Your arises, make any sense
I don't know what to do with my words
I don't know what to do
Doid? Bibimbap is actually pronounced more like bibimbap, what?
Nice distraction, you spin on me
Did you know that Tani?
Don't drag him into your crazy
So how have you pronounced it all your life?
Bibimbap
Pedestrian
Just gonna keep ignoring me, huh?
Pop means rice, so if you think about it, bibimbap is oodles closer to what it should be
Interesting
Apply that same smug intellectualism to your exams
We'll be fine, exams aren't like right now
Let's all just wing it
She's gay
Wow, you guys, your ambition is so inspiring
Just don't wait till the last second to copy my notes this time, okay?
Don't you wah me?
If you're gonna copy them, just do it now
Better yet, we're all gonna have a study session
Ew
Hey, has anyone seen Taita?
I think he said he had a training thing at his new part-time job
Oh, hey, where are you going, Tani? Study with us
Me?
No, thanks
Aw, man
Homeboy's acting like he's already got this in the bag
Maybe he just correctly assumes there's no value in studying with us
Ah, he's just a busy boy
Tani has to go to work in the library after class
Ah, that hurts less
How are we supposed to know that?
Bru needs some more lines
Wait a minute, guys, you thinking what I'm thinking?
Hells yes
To the library we go
Okay, dinguses, let's start by consolidating notes
Ooh, your notebooks always look so shrinking
You probably decorate them more than you study
At least mine have actual information in them
Yeesh, what is this lecture even from?
These notes don't ring a bell at all
Of course they don't, you were probably asleep
This is fine, my backup plan is opening the eighth gate
You're gonna die for a D?
And... done!
Ma'am, that was a lot of work
You literally did nothing but copy my notes
Get a grip
This is the best I've ever felt before a test
Maybe this time I'll level up and get a 60
So, about this homework, where's the answer key?
Why don't you dust off your brain and use it for once?
Tani, help your boy
Help your girl first
Hey, shoo!
And that's why the X would equal three
Does that make sense?
Wow, you're a bomb tutor
Thanks, bro!
Yo, wait!
We should be roomies when we go to Utokyo!
Let's not get ahead of ourselves
We're at least gonna get straight A's, right?
I'm afraid I have no comment
Oh my god!
We're so sweaty!
Speechless!
What's with the weirdo's smile?
Oh!
Nothing!
It's just...
It's really cool seeing my friends and boyfriend get along so well
I guess I'm just happy?
And when I get happy, I get the wiggles
Huh...
I think I kinda get it
He wasn't a part of the group before
And now he's blending in like he's one of the boys
Exactly!
I'm totally getting into Utokyo!
Not before me, you won't
I've got a way better chance than you, though!
Haha!
There's no way!
Also rude!
Think I could become friends with him, too?
You kidding me?
Of course you can!
You're actually the most like him out of everybody
Uh-huh
Well, I think it's safe to say we're done here!
Thanks to Tani!
I know everything about everything now!
That's great to hear
Don't miss me too much when I go to Utokyo, okay?
I'm afraid I have no comment
Haha!
That's so funny!
Tani reacted the exact same way!
You guys are perfectly in sync
And that would make us like soulmates!
What was that?
Whatever!
Yamada, he's not a homework machine!
Wow, she's never gonna learn how to run
Oh yeah, thank god!
Hey Tani, do you wanna get out of here?
Excuse me, are you picking up on him like some sleazebag at a bar?
Hooray!
Time to touch grass!
Good job, you guys!
Great job!
Sorry
They're a lot near a saint
No
We usually don't get a lot of people in the library
This was fun
That was his idea of fun?
Hey!
We should grab a bite to eat somewhere!
What are you all in the mood for?
Hmmmm
Ow!
Peep2bop!
Maybe peep1bop?
Peep1bop it is!
Let's gooo!
Bop?
Oh my god!
You actually said peep1bop!
That's hilarious!
I said Peep-a-pop! That's hilarious!
Well, you did tell me earlier that pop is the right way to say it.
I mean, yeah, but...
bop's easy to say.
Goes off the tongue.
Suzuki can be like them sometimes.
Hang in there, Tani.
Thanks.
Oh!
Were you guys talking about me just now?
Nah, you're not that big of a deal.
Dudes, you're slowing us down!
Do you want to get Bibimbap or not?
Of course I boppin' do!
Let's go!
What is this?
I thought I'd come in a stone pot.
Yeah.
Girl, just eat it.
I'm usually super chill, but sometimes I get excited.
For example, when a convenience store opens close to the crib.
And today's the day!
Gonna hit up the stars!
Bye!
Hold on.
Before you go, could you pick up some toilet paper for us, please?
Mom, the TP prices will be jacked.
Maybe, but we've only got about a third of a roll left.
You're right, that is dire.
Oh, you're seriously going out looking like that?
Hide the children.
Ah, crap.
We got demons.
Grab a pack of Luckies for me.
Cancer sticks!
I guess he does have a point.
I'd never intentionally let Tani see me like this.
Gotta look hot for my boy.
What the?
Huh?
You had nothing better to do either!
Did you bring the coupons too?
Bet your booty.
Are those our gym shorts from middle school?
Never thought I'd see them in public.
Yeah, and what about those off-brand, high-water, glamour, don't track pants?
I'll eat you alive, bro.
Hurtful.
Huh?
Will you look at that?
Howdy, Taito!
Please don't make a big scene at our grand opening.
Challenge accepted.
Wait a sec, don't you live pretty far away from here?
This place is close to school, it's easy to get to on weekdays.
And I won't bump into anybody I know from middle school.
What?
Why wouldn't you want to see your friends at work?
The register area is for checkout only.
As a courtesy to your fellow customers, please make your purchase and exit.
Give it up, we know the real you.
Dear diary, today I endured the abject humiliation of buying toilet paper from someone I know.
Don't be embarrassed, we all shiz.
Will you two just get out of here already?
Later, Tara!
We'll see you a few hours from now when we get the late night munchies!
We'll be closed, idiots.
Huh?
Uh, another excellent wreck from Capaccio.
Not bad, Capaccio.
I forget, did it rain today?
Uh, I think it kind of like misted, but it stopped pretty quick.
That's what I thought.
Nature always smells nice after rain.
Smells the same to me.
Uh, well, you know, the dirt microbes.
Uh, forget I said anything.
I just heard a hog!
Is that the cops?
What?
I was late!
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, doo-doo-doo-doo.
Howdy!
Hey! What the heck are you doing here?
I was just out doing donuts on my sweet chopper.
You know, Drifton, saw this place and I thought I'd shake it down.
I think you're the one the cops should be worried about.
Whew, thought you guys were a junkie couple and were either gonna mug me or suck face.
I don't know which one would be where's TBA.
You can't recognize us from more than five feet away.
Dang, girl, you really don't care what you look like after school's out.
Shut up! I wasn't expecting a reunion!
I'm telling you as a friend, it's the shorts.
What do you think Tani would say if we saw you right now?
What? So not happening. Don't scare me like that.
You don't look too different from normal.
Shut your butt!
I've got nothing to worry about.
Tani wouldn't randomly pull up to a convenience store in the middle of the...
Whoa. Hey, Suzuki.
Oh, hey, Yamada and hey, Watanabe.
Too slow.
Hey, why are you out on a school night?
Are you out selling hugs?
I could ask you the same thing.
So, um, where's Suzuki?
I don't know what you mean, bro.
Why don't you get on in there and do shopping?
We were never here. This is all just a bad dream.
What?
Could you please say something, dude?
Run! Quick before he sees the shorts!
He thinks he's asleep, so you're safe.
I'm in your debt!
Hey, that's my helmet!
I'm sorry, Tani. I want you to see most versions of me.
You just can't see this one.
I'm taking makeup-less goblin Suzuki and her ratty gym shorts to my grave.
I'll never let you see my disappointing, not-hot self.
Never!
Okay, you can't catch me now.
Eat my dust, Achilles. I'm the mother-flipping donut!
Suzuki, wait.
Oh, dear Pits, Achilles.
Why are you running away?
I look gross!
You do know that none of that bothers me, right?
I know you don't think it's a big deal, but it bothers the crap out of me.
My carefully crafted vibes are in ruins.
Is that so?
Why don't you care if Yamada sees you like this?
Huh?
Because I don't vibe with Yamada like that.
I've known him since middle school. I don't care how I look with him.
And Taira and Watanabe?
Let's see. Nabe and I met our first year of high school, and Taira...
Well, he's just Taira, you feel me?
I see.
Excuse me. You're clearly upset. How come you're running away from me?
I'm not the one who literally ran away tonight.
Wow. Sassy.
It's just, you've known your friends for so much longer than you've known me, I get a little jealous sometimes.
Listen, Tawny. Imagine I have two plates, okay? Now, one's a pile of eggs and rice on a paper plate, and the other's perfect omu rice on a fancy platter.
Even if they taste the exact same, it doesn't matter because I'm always going to want to give you the nicer dish.
I want to be the nice rice! Let me serve!
But I don't care about how it's presented. None of that matters to me as long as I like the food.
Wait. That kind of sucks.
Why?
If you see a carefully crafted bougie dessert, you gotta acknowledge it and say, wow, that's so pretty, or this is beautiful, to show respect.
Respect? For the vibes.
Exactly! For the vibes!
Slow down! Let me ride on the back.
If you want. But it might get wobbly.
Wobble it up, wobble boy!
Oh, man, that feels good!
Um, Tawny, you know how summer nights have this unique kind of feel to them? Like a special mood?
Well, I think it's one of the best feelings there is.
I do, too.
And it smells nice.
I love the scent in the air after it rains.
Yeah, I love it, too.
Huh?
Aren't you Suzuki's sister? Go home before I call your mom!
Aye-aye, sir!
Should I be worried about her criminal record?
Hup, hup!
Eee! I'm gonna die of hype! The festival's almost here!
You sure I've perked up now that finals are over.
So are you guys going to the widow event?
Uh-huh. Fireworks rule, but it's always a bloodbath finding a good spot just to wait hours for the show to start, and then taking the train home is like fighting off a mob.
Cold, hard fats.
Should I wear a yukita, or is that too over the top?
What? Don't be ridiculous! Of course you should wear one!
Who knows how much longer you have as a couple!
What did you say?
Don't put that negative to me!
I'm just saying you should think about the air!
No one's asking!
In Ambe-speak, that means say what you feel and don't take him for granted.
Yes.
Wow, wise.
That said, don't become one of those couples who can't turn the mush off.
As if!
I wonder what he'll think. Maybe I overdid it? Or maybe I didn't do enough? Should I have gone to the salon? How did people manage to cram everything into these tiny drawstring bags? Are folk sandals, like, obscenely tacky?
Gosh, I'm sweating so much, my makeup's gonna be soup!
No! Get your ish together, girl! You can do this!
Tani!
Sorry for the wait.
Yukita?
Yeah, so, you like it?
You're beautiful.
Prior to this moment, I might have occasionally cleared the cute bar, but I think this is the first time anyone's ever called me beautiful!
Let's rage, Tani! Time to tear it up!
Yeah!
I don't think we need to go that far.
Whoa! Don't you just love all the sights and sounds?
Yeah.
I'm gonna scan the boots real quick and decide what to get. Let me know if you want anything, okay?
Hey, watch out behind you.
I'm sorry!
It's all good.
Guess this is the danger zone.
Gotta be careful with the herd around, am I right?
Yeah, right.
What's up?
You and me! We're like a legit couple.
Oh, man. This is exactly what Sato warned me about.
I see Tani every day at school, but that's why being out like this feels extra special and soups romantic.
I gotta be cool.
I can't let myself get lost in the sauce.
Yummy!
Nope, too late.
I just can't help myself!
Yay!
At a time like this, how could I not turn into a mega-mushy-mush-ball?
Wah!
Holy god, boy can scoop!
You didn't have to share one with little ol' me.
That's fine. You can take both of them if you want.
But they're your trophies.
Oh, let me know if you need to wipe your hands. I packed a metric crap ton of these bad boys.
You're so prepared.
Duh! I made a checklist for tonight!
I mean, Noah didn't! I'm just really chic and smart!
Thank you.
Could this night get any better?
I love you, Taku!
I love you, too!
Groanie!
This is a gosh dang family event, people!
R.I.P. my eyes!
Is that what happens when your giddy meter maxes out and you turn into a mush monster?
I guess I can't be too weirded out.
Deep down inside, part of me totally gets how they feel.
I'm cool as a cucumber when Tawny's not around.
It's easy to assume I'm not going to act a certain way or lose sight of everything when he's not right in front of me.
And yet...
What have I been like this entire night?
Oh, God!
I'm the mush monster!
What have I become?
Something wrong?
Do you need to get home by a certain time?
No, it's not that.
Mind if we take a little walk?
Sure.
I've never come up this way before.
The road's getting steeper and steeper.
Where could he be taking us?
A make-out spot!
Already?
We're here.
There's a lot of people here.
Yeah.
Whoa!
So, no smooching.
Why did he bring us here?
Makes me kind of nervous.
I'm bored!
When are the fireworks going to start?
Just be patient.
They'll start soon.
Huh?
Holy smokes!
Is that the fireworks show we skipped out on?
You can see them from here?
Sorry I couldn't get us closer.
Who cares?
This is totally awesome!
Thank you.
For everything.
Wonder if my camera can catch them.
They're far away, so it might not work.
Yeah.
Too bad.
I'll have to burn them into my brain.
That was a close one.
Whoa!
Awesome!
OMG!
We came so, so close to kissing!
Actually, maybe we should have.
Crap.
Well, now I totally want to.
Suzuki?
Ah!
Next time, let's get even closer.
Hang on!
Closer?
Like, you really wanna...
Closer to the show.
We can go next year.
If you want.
Oh, yeah!
Let's go!
He said next year!
I'm gonna die!
So, how was your festival date?
Oh, yeah!
Your girl scored Big Ten!
Yeah, that's Super Bowl.
Oh, yeah!
Yeah, hey!
お決まりのフレーズは
引き出しの中へ
何よりも振り切って
声を出してみる
鏡の奥まで
目を凝らして
Ah, jigsaw na
道を抜け 居合わせた影も 曇る窓へ描くように 縁取ってほしい 言葉で透き通ったり 縮む幻 差し込めた 火を踏んで 跳ねた色も 少しだけ好きになる
ねえ 今を隠されちゃうラインに 意外な魔法をかけ合って わからなくて わからないねって話して
音頭が触った後に 混じってた 匂いが 雨みたいにしたってる